so you want to see what
$799,000 can buy you here in Central
Texas well stick with me as we tour this
luxury custom home builder in belon
Texas this is one of my favorite
communities and favorite Builders and I
know you love it
too hi I'm Andrea dudic associate broker
and realtor with f real estate if you
want to see more homes just like this
don't forget to like this video
subscribe to my channel and click the
Bell icon so you can stay up toate on
all things real estate Happening Here in
Central Texas so this is a K's executive
home I really love this Builder you have
a lot of options when buying or building
with them this is considered a spec home
because it's already complete you
generally get a lot better uh incentives
and deals with spec homes because the
Builder trying to offload their
inventory and cost generally goes up
when you start over um we'll talk more
in later videos about the difference
between spec homes semic custom and
custom home but for purposes of this one
this is a spe home price at
$799,000 so what I really like about
this Builder is that they build to a
really high standard so a lot of the
things that they um standardly put into
their home is considered an upgrade with
some Builders and so your price per
square foot and overall price might be
higher with this but in my opinion you
are getting more within the home um so
we'll start with the kitchen this
kitchen is really beautiful they do a
great job with all of their floor plans
and the kitchen this is a super open
concept home with the kitchen opening
out and looking out into the main living
space we have pet light over at the
beautiful for
[Music]
countertops custom white
cabinet with beautiful black Hardware a
really great great feature of this
community is that they have gas gas is
not standard here in our area um but
this community does have it and so they
have you have propane gas for
your range your stove and then as well
as your outdoor kitchen so that's
great so this is the main living space
it has a wonderful lighting um you have
ceramic tile that looks like throughout
the home floor to ceiling stone
fireplace all to ceilings with a being
running through
it over here you have your formal dining
space with a double tray ceiling which
is really nice and then over here you
could really multi-purpose this room
it's currently being used as an office
which I think looks great with this
fantastic
actionable what you you are great French
drawers
here come back this
way you also have your secondary dining
space your Eventing kitchen I really
like all the fixtures they use
throughout this home now this home has
the wood beef in the main living space
but if they don't have it they typically
will do crown molding standard
throughout the home either Trace
ceilings or double Trace ceilings so
those nice um additions really add to
the I guess elegate finish of the um on
this side we have your master bedroom
this is a split floor
plane you have your master bedroom on
the left and your laundry room on the
right this is very bathroom you
have tile ceramic tile in here double
vanity you have a soaking
tub and a really awesome walk-in shower
with a SE sitting area
dual shower heads with a brain ball
shower
head your commode is separate and you
have a fantastic walk-in closet
probably need a ladder but you could do
your winter clothes up top and rotate
seasonally I'm going to give you a peek
of the other side of the home there's a
lot of privacy with this floor plan with
that the three full baths is really
awesome so you have a full bath on this
side with a bedroom so that they can
have their own space and then a shared
full bathroom over here will be
additional to vomes let's say
[Music]
[Applause]
take a look at this back
patio you have your full outdoor
kitchen propane grill mini fridge and
sink with your full prep
area and you also have an outdoor
fireplace so pretty
and tons of space for you to entertain
with your extended back P so this is the
side of the home you have a three car
garage foursided masy and a beautiful
beautiful front home I hope you enjoyed
this luxury custom home today if you
would like to explore your options on
this home or any others in the area or
maybe you'd like to discuss building
your own custom dream homes you can find
all my contact information below you can
schedule a zoom call or you can text
call and email me I'd love to speak with
you until next time
[Music]